{"subjectID":1,"researchID":"SonificationResearch","dateTime":"2020-12-18T13:39:23.2291859+01:00","answers":[{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":26.97237,"questionAnswerTime":33.17719},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":26.97237,"questionAnswerTime":33.17719},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":37.1202,"questionAnswerTime":41.17439},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 1 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":44.6183929,"questionAnswerTime":44.6183929},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 2 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":45.3185539,"questionAnswerTime":45.3185539},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 3 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":45.8072052,"questionAnswerTime":45.8072052},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 4 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":46.38534,"questionAnswerTime":46.38534},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 5 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":47.9680977,"questionAnswerTime":47.9680977},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":26.97237,"questionAnswerTime":33.17719},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":37.1202,"questionAnswerTime":41.17439},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":66.17396,"questionAnswerTime":83.49626},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":26.97237,"questionAnswerTime":33.17719},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":37.1202,"questionAnswerTime":41.17439},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":66.17396,"questionAnswerTime":83.49626},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.90216,"questionAnswerTime":104.7528},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":26.97237,"questionAnswerTime":33.17719},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":37.1202,"questionAnswerTime":41.17439},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":66.17396,"questionAnswerTime":83.49626},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.90216,"questionAnswerTime":104.7528},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":106.770866,"questionAnswerTime":111.018631}]}